{
    "id": "d8ad79f7d0334cf6ba341faedcfc849e",
    "title": "Inseparable Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He continues to call …………………….. his old colleagues.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "169477bbe48445338df9c5e5620faaaf"
        },
        {
            "question": "It took me quite some time to get………………………. my breakup with Nancy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "704ba30572b64f13bf56f571088d568c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I need to go ……………………. the documents again before I can arrive at a decision.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "over",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "56bb8ee9eaac44daafcf2f6affb59bbe"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has already gone ……………………. all his money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "through",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "225051a99dea45738726204354dc5ccd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Jane has agreed to look ………………… my baby when I am gone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "after",
                "at",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e19304310bb84510b47a4bec85eb47af"
        },
        {
            "question": "The officer said that he would look ………………………. the matter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "at",
                "after"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bf89bd4a3bec4f3992ccbf70c2681cc4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ran ……………………. an old friend of mine yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7575a82f6e2f4248b9a14c2978777a84"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ran …………………… Mary at the super market.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "into",
                "after",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "be461793c68844aca85b968614155dcf"
        },
        {
            "question": "I look forward …………………….. hearing from you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5b355b1a895945e1885da100c818051a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I couldn’t believe my eyes when I saw my old boss waiting ……………………. tables.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3a9ab64b5a7b4aefb68d36abecf0e834"
        }
    ]
}